export const data = [
    {
        question: "Who is the G.O.A.T of Football?",
        option1: "Cristiano Ronaldo",
        option2: "Pele",
        option3: "Lionel Messi",
        option4: "Diego Maradona",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the 'Greezly Bear'?",
        option1: "Soutrik Ghosh",
        option2: "Debojyoti Mitra",
        option3: "Big Show",
        option4: "Mark Henry",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Arnab's Future Wife?",
        option1: "Rup",
        option2: "Debojyoti",
        option3: "P..",
        option4: "Bidishikha",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Roni's Future Wife?",
        option1: "Sneha",
        option2: "Rup",
        option3: "Secret Crush",
        option4: "Forever Single",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Will 'MOON' Come to me in future?",
        option1: "Yes",
        option2: "No",
        option3: "Never",
        option4: "In Imagination",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Who is 'The Gay' of Discord Gang?",
        option1: "Rup",
        option2: "Baap Kelane Sayan",
        option3: "Roni",
        option4: "Dani",
        ans: 3,
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Rishav's Future Wife?",
        option1: "P..",
        option2: "S..",
        option3: "Naru",
        option4: "Bagchi",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Who is The 'GrandPa' of the Discord Server?",
        option1: "Sahitya The Don",
        option2: "Rishav The Chapri",
        option3: "Arnab The Kalua",
        option4: "Big Bro Debojyoti",
        ans: 1,
    },
    {
        question: "Who is the 'MagiBaaz'?",
        option1: "Rup",
        option2: "Naru",
        option3: "Anshu",
        option4: "Rishav",
        ans: 2,
    },
    {
        question: "Who is 'Chamcha' of the Discord Gang",
        option1: "Rup",
        option2: "Jeet",
        option3: "Roni",
        option4: "Dani",
        ans: 1,
    }
];
